<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Developer Blog on Archmage</title><link>https://www.archmage.fi/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Developer Blog on Archmage</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.archmage.fi/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Verifying Pixel Cats</title><link>https://www.archmage.fi/posts/verifying-pixel-cats/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.archmage.fi/posts/verifying-pixel-cats/</guid><description>Now that minting has started on Pixel Cats, owners might want to know how to verify that their cat is contained within the preset provenance hash. There are two ways you could do this - on-chain or off-chain.
On-Chain Head over to the contract on FTMScan and find your token id by entering your address and 0 as the index on the tokenOfOwnerByIndex function. Press the query button and it will return the token id that you own.</description></item><item><title>Pixel Cats</title><link>https://www.archmage.fi/posts/pixel-cats-into-apr-2022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.archmage.fi/posts/pixel-cats-into-apr-2022/</guid><description>On Sunday 17th April 2022 1800 UTC minting will go live on our newly released Pixel Cats NFT project on the Fantom ecosystem. The entire project will be open sourced, allowing artists and developers to fork the code and use it for themselves to get a huge headstart on creating their own projects. Head on over to the NFT site to get the rundown on the more basic details, like why it&amp;rsquo;s being released on Fantom, and how many can be minted at a time, etc.</description></item><item><title>Cap.finance Dashboard</title><link>https://www.archmage.fi/posts/cap-dashboard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.archmage.fi/posts/cap-dashboard/</guid><description>On the arbitrum network there is a neat platform called Cap.finance that allows users wanting to earn yield on their ETH or USDC to become the casino and allow traders limited use of their funds as leverage. Due to the age old phrase &amp;lsquo;The House always wins&amp;rsquo;, it follows that over time the pools will increase in size as traders, on average, lose.
Archmage Dashboard What&amp;rsquo;s lacking is a good way to view if traders are winning or losing overall and the general health of the dapp.</description></item><item><title>Roadmap &amp; The Graph</title><link>https://www.archmage.fi/posts/roadmap-2022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.archmage.fi/posts/roadmap-2022/</guid><description>In the last round of Graph grants, Archmage was awarded a grant to build the supporting infrastructure to help The Graph grow. The main purpose of the grant was to deploy new subgraphs and a front end to provide tooling for market makers to make well-informed decisions as to where they should allocate their capital.
Subgraphs Archmage has already released new Uniswap V3 subgraphs to the hosted service - Uniswap V3, and Uniswap V3 Minimal.</description></item></channel></rss>